Poonpittinan Yupa

- Back-end Developer -

Mobile: +66 98-553-5964 | Gmail: poonpittinan.in@gmail.com LinkedIn: Poonpittinan Yupa | Github: https://github.com/Poonpit

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate back-end developer who has experience in coding multiple programming languages, developing, planning, manage projects, designing features skill and strong understanding of multiple software applications design tools and languages. Would like to join the experience at Magic Box Solutions Co., Ltd. Able to develop in back-end development. Have the ability to self-motivated and good communication skills to learn and develop projects with your company to achieve goals.

SKILLS			
Languages	DBMS	Web Development	Others
Golang	MySQL	React	Git
Python	MongoDB	NodeJS	Postman
TypeScript / JavaScript		ExpressJS	00P
Java		ASP .Net Core 5	
HTML / CSS		Entity Framework	
C#		Material UI	

EDUCATION

CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY

2020 - 2024

Faculty of Science, Department of Computer Science, GPA 3.31

EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP

Employee Evaluation System MAY 2023 - SEP 2023 Front-End Web Developer

- · Designed UX/UI.
- Created an authentication system and maintain system security.
- Utilizes RESTful APIs to create endpoints for calling APIs within the back-end system.
- Developed features in various parts of the employee evaluation system in the front end.
- Controlled various routes of the system according to roles and positions in accordance with specified conditions.
- Pull data from the database to display in dashboards.

Candidate Evaluation System APR 2023 - MAY 2023 Full-stack Web Developer

- Won the UX/UI design contest for the candidate evaluation system.
- Managed database structure in ASP .Net Core 5 projects that use Entity Framework Core to connect and manage databases.
- The system uses the Hexagonal Architecture model.
- Dynamic display organization all within the system.
- Developed various displays to meet the requirement of actual users.

COURSEWORK PROJECT

Medical Information System SEP 2022 - OCT 2022 Full-stack Web Developer

- · Managed database in profile feature.
- Managed and operated database to receive data from responses questionnaires.
- Utilizes React for rendering the questionnaire inputs.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Telephone Number Application JUL 2022 - AUG 2022 Front-End Web Developer

• Created to store names and phone numbers by using pure React.

Product Management Application JUL 2022 - AUG 2022 Back-End Web Developer

- Developed a product management system.
- Used Cookies & Sessions to manage the login system with NodeJS.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Teacher Assistant for Al Course MAR 2022 - APR 2022
Young Computer Scientist Camp

- Taught an AI course in Python for high school students from 14 schools.
- Received a good response from the evaluation.

Teacher Assistant for Python JUN 2021 - AUG 2021 Course Programming

• Taught 100 hours of Python for first-year students.

CERTIFICATES

- AWS Academy Graduate AWS Academy Cloud Foundations
- Advent of Cyber 2022 (Basic Cyber Security Knowledge and Experience)

22 MAR 2024